Redwood Canyon Ramblers collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographic materials
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, August 5, 1959, Phil Olivier; 1959-08-05 RCR by PO 1.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, August 5, 1959, Phil Olivier; 1959-08-05 RCR by PO 2.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, August 5, 1959, Phil Olivier; 1959-08-05 RCR by PO 3.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, August 5, 1959, Phil Olivier; 1959-08-05 RCR by PO 4.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, August 5, 1959, Phil Olivier; 1959-08-05 RCR by PO 5.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, August 5, 1959, Phil Olivier; 1959-08-05 RCR by PO 6.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, August 5, 1959, Phil Olivier; 1959-08-05 RCR by PO 7.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, August 5, 1959, Phil Olivier; 1959-08-05 RCR by PO 8.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Hootenanny at Studio Q (San Francisco), featuring the Redwood Canyon Ramblers [flyer], September 9, 1959, 1959-09-09 RCR SF Hoot.jpg; 1 photograph: color, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers in concert, August 27, 1960, 1960-09-00 RCR at unknown location 1.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers in concert, September 1960, 1960-09-00 RCR at unknown location 2.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers in concert, April 1963, 1963-04-00.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Scott Hambly and Al Berg in concert; third man not identified, April 1963, 1963-04-00hambly al and berg.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at The Cabale, August 1963, 1963-08-00 RCR at Cabale 1.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at The Cabale, August 1963, 1963-08-00 RCR at Cabale 2.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at The Cabale, August 1963, 1963-08-00 RCR at Cabale 3.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at The Cabale, August 1963, 1963-08-00 RCR at Cabale 4.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at The Cabale, August 1963, 1963-08-00 RCR at Cabale 5.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Pigeon Hill Boys at Purdue University, 1963-1964, Pigeon-Hill-Purdue-1_63-64_.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Pigeon Hill Boys at Purdue University, 1963-1964, Pigeon-Hill-Purdue-2_63-64_.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, June 1988, RCR2-6-88-bySR.jpg; 1 photograph: color, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, June 1988, RCR-6-88-bySR.jpg; 1 photograph: color, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, June 11, 2008, 2008-06-11.pdf; 1 photograph: color, digital (.jpg)
  - Flyer for Redwood Canyon Ramblers, undated, bearslair_low by Rick Shubb.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Framed flyer for a folk singing performance by Neil Rosenberg, at Gull Bookshop, Port Richmond, undated, IMG_2658.jpg; 1 photograph: color, digital (.jpg)